Guide to the Greenwich House Records TAM.139
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VI: Scrapbooks (Partially microfilmed)
  - Subseries B: Music School Scrapbooks (boxes 50-59 have NOT been microfilmed)
    - Greenwich House Music School - Scrapbook 13, 1944-1945 (Box 53, Folder 1-4)
    - Greenwich House Music School - Scrapbook 14, 1945-1946 (Box 53, Folder 5-7)
    - Greenwich House Music School - Scrapbook 15, 1946-1947 (Box 54, Folder 1-3)
    - Greenwich House Music School - Scrapbook 16, 1947-1948 (Box 54, Folder 4-6)
    - Greenwich House Music School - Scrapbook 17, 1948-1949 (Box 54, Folder 7-9)
    - Greenwich House Music School - Scrapbook, 1949-1950 (Box 55, Folder SB 18)
    - Greenwich House Music School - Scrapbook, 1950-1951 (Box 55, Folder SB 19)
    - Greenwich House Music School - Scrapbook, 1952-1953 (Box 55, Folder SB 20)
    - Greenwich House Music School - Scrapbook, 1953-1954 (Box 56, Folder SB 21)
    - Greenwich House Music School - Scrapbook, 1954-1955 (Box 56, Folder SB 22)
    - Greenwich House Music School - Scrapbook, 1956-1957 (Box 56, Folder SB 23)
    - Greenwich House Music School - Scrapbook, 1957-1958 (Box 57, Folder SB 24)
    - Greenwich House Music School - Scrapbook, 1958-1959 (Box 57, Folder SB 25)
    - Greenwich House Music School - Scrapbook, 1959-1960 (Box 57, Folder SB 26)
    - Greenwich House Music School - Scrapbook, 1960-1961 (Box 57, Folder SB 27)
    - Greenwich House Music School - Scrapbook, 1961-1962 (Box 57, Folder SB 28)
    - Greenwich House Music School - Scrapbook, 1962-1963 (Box 57, Folder SB 29)
    - Greenwich House Music School - Scrapbook, 1963-1964 (Box 57, Folder SB 30)
    - Greenwich House Music School - Scrapbook, 1964-1965 (Box 57, Folder SB 31)
    - Greenwich House Music School - Scrapbook, 1965-1966 (Box 57, Folder SB 32)
    - Greenwich House Music School - Scrapbook, 1966-1967 (Box 58, Folder SB 33)
    - Greenwich House Music School - Scrapbook, 1967-1968 (Box 58, Folder SB 34)
    - Greenwich House Music School - Scrapbook, 1968-1969 (Box 58, Folder SB 35)
    - Greenwich House Music School - Scrapbook, 1969-1970 (Box 58, Folder SB 36)
    - Greenwich House Music School - Scrapbook, 1970-1971 (Box 58, Folder SB 37)
    - Greenwich House Music School - Scrapbook, 1971-1972 (Box 58, Folder SB 38)
    - Greenwich House Music School - Scrapbook, 1972-1973 (Box 59, Folder SB 39)
    - Greenwich House Music School - Scrapbook, 1973-1974 (Box 59, Folder SB 40)
    - Greenwich House Music School - Scrapbook, 1974-1975 (Box 59, Folder SB 41)
    - Greenwich House Music School - Scrapbook, 1975-1976 (Box 59, Folder SB 42)
    - Greenwich House Music School - Scrapbook, 1976-1977 (Box 59, Folder SB 43)
    - Greenwich House Music School - Scrapbook, 1977-1978 (Box 59, Folder SB 44)
    - Greenwich House Music School - Scrapbook, 1978-1979 (Box 59, Folder SB 45)
    - Greenwich House Music School - Scrapbooks Addendum (26 scrapbooks), 1980-2009 (Box 128, Box 129, Box 130, Box 131, Box 132, Box 133, Box 134, Box 136, Box 135, Box 137, Box 138, Box 139)
    - Greenwich House Music School - Scrapbook, Marion Rous, 1924-1967; 2015.061 (Box 124)
- Series VII: Greenwich House Index Card Files (NOT microfilmed)
  Organization: Series VII: Greenwich House Index Card Files
  Suberies A: Individuals: Clients, Neighborhood, Volunteers, Others.
  Subseries B: Club, Individual and Family Record Cards (oversized, 5x8)
  Subseries C: Greenwich House Library Catalog
  Subseries D: Greenwich House Children's Theater and Music School
  Subseries E: Henry Street Settlement Visiting Nurses
  - Suberies A: Individuals: Clients, Neighborhood, Volunteers, Others.
    - A-Att, undated (Box 61)
    - Att-Ber, undated (Box 62)
    - Ber-Bri, undated (Box 63)
    - Bro-Cap, undated (Box 64)
    - Cap-Cer, undated (Box 65)
    - Cer-Con, undated (Box 66)
    - Con-Daz, undated (Box 67)
    - DeA-DiG, undated (Box 68)
    - DiG-Esp, undated (Box 69)
    - Esp-Fox, undated (Box 70)
    - Fox-Gia, undated (Box 71)
    - Gia-Guz, undated (Box 72)
    - H-Hur, undated (Box 73)
    - Hur-Kir, undated (Box 74)
    - Kir-Lev, undated (Box 75)
    - Lew-McK, undated (Box 76)
    - McK-Mar, undated (Box 77)
    - Mar-Mon, undated (Box 78)
    - Mon-Nyl, undated (Box 79)
    - O-Pat, undated (Box 80)
    - Pat-Pow, undated (Box 81)
    - Pow-Riz, undated (Box 82)
    - Roa-San, undated (Box 83)
    - San-Sid, undated (Box 84)
    - Sid-Sul, undated (Box 85)
    - Sul-Tza, undated (Box 86)
    - U-Wil, undated (Box 87)
    - Wil-Zva, undated (Box 88)
  - Subseries B: Club, Individual and Family Record Cards (oversized, 5x8)
    - Club, Individual and Family Record Cards (oversized, 5x8), 1915 (Box 88A)
  - Subseries C: Greenwich House Library Catalog
    - Library of Greenwich House, undated (Box 89)
  - Subseries D: Greenwich House Children's Theater and Music School
    - Greenwich House Children's Theater and Music School, 1949-1967 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Subseries E: Henry Street Settlement Visiting Nurses
    - Henry Street Settlement Visiting Nurses, 1910-1916 (Box 90, Folder 2)
- Series VIII: Greenwich House post-Simkhovitch records (NOT microfilmed)
  Organization: Series VIII: Greenwich House post-Simkhovitch records
  Subseries 1: Annual Reports, Monthly Reports, Minutes, and Miscellaneous
  Subseries 2: Director's Files
  Subseries 3: Maxwell Powers Files
  Subseries 4: FundraisingContribution Correspondence- Individuals (alphabetically)FoundationsContributions
  Subseries 5: New York House & School of Industry (NYHSI)
  Subseries 6: Miscellaneous
  Subseries 7: Music School
  Subseries 8: Pottery School
  Subseries 9: United Neighborhood Houses (UNH)
  Subseries 10: National Federation of Settlements
  Subseries 11: Benefits
  Subseries 12: Executive Director's Files--1950-1979 (UNPROCESSED PORTION)
  Subseries 13: General (UNPROCESSED PORTION)
  - Subseries 1: Annual Reports, Monthly Reports, Minutes, and Miscellaneous
    - Contribution Lists, 1947 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Contribution Lists, 1948 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Contribution Lists, 1949 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Contributor's Lists, 1950 (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - List of Contributing Foundations, 1950-1952 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - Record of Contributions by Foundations between 1906-1949 (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Contributors' Lists, 1956-1957 (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Reports on Fundraising, 1956-1957 (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - Record of Contributing Foundations (1907-51), 1951 (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - Contribution Correspondence- Foundations, A-Z, 1951-1955 (Box 91, Folder 10)
    - Contribution- Special Appeals, 1969 (Box 91, Folder 11)
    - Contributors' Lists, 1954-1955 (Box 91, Folder 12)
    - Contributors' Lists, 1958 (Box 91, Folder 13)
    - Fundraising Letters, 1947-1952 (Box 91, Folder 14)
    - Financial Records- Monthly Reports, 1955 (Box 91, Folder 15)
    - Financial Records- Statements, 1946-1975 (Box 91, Folder 16)
    - Financial Records- Budgets, Financial Statements, 1981 (Box 91, Folder 17)
    - Financial Records- Audit Report; Financial Statements, 1980 (Box 91, Folder 18)
    - Paid Workers- Camp Employment Contracts, A-Z, 1954 (Box 91, Folder 19)
    - Paid Workers- Camp Staff, A-Z, 1955 (Box 91, Folder 20)
    - Paid Workers- Camp Staff, A-Z, 1964 (Box 91, Folder 21)
    - Paid Workers- Camp Staff Medical Records, A-Z, 1964 (Box 91, Folder 22)
    - Paid Workers- Camp Staff, A-M, 1965 (Box 91, Folder 23)
    - Paid Workers- Camp Staff, M-Z, 1965 (Box 91, Folder 24)
    - Paid Workers- Camp Staff Medical Records, 1965 (Box 91, Folder 25)
    - Board of Managers- lists, undated (Box 91, Folder 26)
    - Annual Luncheon, 1969 (Box 91, Folder 27)
    - Annual Luncheon, 1970 (Box 91, Folder 28)
    - Annual Luncheon, 1971 (Box 91, Folder 29)
    - Annual Luncheon, 1973 (Box 91, Folder 30)
    - Annual Luncheon, 1974 (Box 91, Folder 31)
    - Annual Luncheon, 1975 (Box 91, Folder 32)
    - Minutes- Annual Meetings, undated (Box 91, Folder 33)
    - History of GH/ organizational structure, undated (Box 91, Folder 34)
    - Memorandum on Objectives & Program of GH, 1946 (Box 91, Folder 35)
    - Annual Reports, 1947-1950 (Box 91, Folder 36)
    - Annual Report, 1952 (Box 91, Folder 37)
    - Annual Reports, 1954-1962 (Box 91, Folder 38)
    - Monthly Reports, 1947 (Box 91, Folder 39)
    - Director's Reports, 1948 (Box 91, Folder 40)
    - Director's Reports, 1949 (Box 91, Folder 41)
    - Director's Reports, 1950 (Box 91, Folder 42)
    - Director's Reports, 1951 (Box 91, Folder 43)
    - Director's Reports, 1952-1954 (Box 91, Folder 44)
    - Director's Reports, 1962-1963 (Box 91, Folder 45)
    - Minutes- Board of Managers; Executive Committee, 1947 (Box 91, Folder 46)
    - Minutes- Board of Managers; Executive Committee, 1948 (Box 91, Folder 47)
    - Minutes- Board of Managers; Executive Committee, 1949 (Box 91, Folder 48)
    - Minutes- Board of Managers, 1950 (Box 91, Folder 49)
    - Minutes- Board of Managers, 1951 (Box 91, Folder 50)
    - Minutes- Board of Managers, 1952 (Box 91, Folder 51)
    - Minutes- Board of Managers, 1953 (Box 91, Folder 52)
    - Minutes- Board of Managers, 1954 (Box 91, Folder 53)
    - Minutes- Board of Managers, 1955 (Box 91, Folder 54)
    - Minutes- Board of Managers, 1958 (Box 91, Folder 55)
    - Minutes- Board of Managers, 1959 (Box 91, Folder 56)
    - Minutes- Board of Managers, 1962 (Box 91, Folder 57)
    - Minutes- Board of Managers, 1963-1964 (Box 91, Folder 58)
    - Minutes- Board of Managers, 1965-1966 (Box 91, Folder 59)
    - Minutes- Board of Managers, 1970-1972 (Box 91, Folder 60)
    - Minutes- Board of Managers, 1973-1975 (Box 91, Folder 61)
    - Minutes- Staff Meetings, 1947-1949 (Box 91, Folder 62)
    - Minutes- Staff Meetings, 1950-1951 (Box 91, Folder 63)
    - Minutes- Staff Meetings, 1951-1952 (Box 91, Folder 64)
    - Minutes- Staff Meetings, 1953-1955 (Box 91, Folder 65)
    - Minutes- Staff Meetings, 1957-1958 (Box 91, Folder 66)
    - Minutes- Staff Meetings, ca.1946, undated (Box 91, Folder 67)
    - Treasurer's Correspondence- Insurance, 1950-1952 (Box 91, Folder 68)
    - Misc., 1974-1975 (Box 91, Folder 69)
  - Subseries 2: Director's Files
    - A, 1948-1949 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - B, 1947-1949 (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - Basham, Harvey A., Jr., 1947-1949 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Board of Education, 1946-1949 (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Board of Managers (Greenwich House), 1948-1949 (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - C, 1948-1949 (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - Childcare Center, 1948-1949 (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - City College of New York, 1946-1949 (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - Condolence letters, 1948-1949 (Box 92, Folder 9)
    - D, 1946 (Box 92, Folder 10)
    - DeSapio, Carmine, 1949 (Box 92, Folder 11)
    - Donations, 1946-1949 (Box 92, Folder 12)
    - Dorr, John V.N., 1949 (Box 92, Folder 13)
    - Elser, Helen, 1948-1949 (Box 92, Folder 14)
    - Farley, James A., 1948-1949 (Box 92, Folder 15)
    - Field, Marshall, 1947 (Box 92, Folder 16)
    - Forums, 1949 (Box 92, Folder 17)
    - H, 1948-1949 (Box 92, Folder 18)
    - I, 1946-1948 (Box 92, Folder 19)
    - Inter-office Communication, 1947-1949 (Box 92, Folder 20)
    - Isaacs, Stanley M., 1946, 1949 (Box 92, Folder 21)
    - Ives, Irving M., 1949 (Box 92, Folder 22)
    - K, 1946-1949 (Box 92, Folder 23)
    - L, 1947-1949 (Box 92, Folder 24)
    - Lehman, Herbert H., 1949 (Box 92, Folder 25)
    - M, 1947-1950 (Box 92, Folder 26)
    - McNulty, Arthur P., 1946-1949 (Box 92, Folder 27)
    - Metcalf, Manton, 1946-1949 (Box 92, Folder 28)
    - Mitchell, MacNeil, 1946-1949 (Box 92, Folder 29)
    - N, 1948-1950 (Box 92, Folder 30)
    - New York Adult Education Council, 1946-1950 (Box 92, Folder 31)
    - New York City Housing Authority- Simkhovitch reappointment, 1948 (Box 92, Folder 32)
    - New York School for Social Work, 1949-1950 (Box 92, Folder 33)
    - New York University, 1946-1950 (Box 92, Folder 34)
    - New York University- Professor Louis R. Sprigg, 1949-1950 (Box 92, Folder 35)
    - O'Dwyer, William, 1949-1950 (Box 92, Folder 36)
    - Ohio State University- Social Administration Library, 1948 (Box 92, Folder 37)
    - P, 1948-1950 (Box 92, Folder 38)
    - Plum, Matthias, 1949 (Box 92, Folder 39)
    - Police Department, 1946-1950 (Box 92, Folder 40)
    - Public Schools 3 and 41, 1949 (Box 92, Folder 41)
    - Queens College, 1947-1950 (Box 92, Folder 42)
    - R, 1948-1951 (Box 92, Folder 43)
    - Rentals, 1947-1950 (Box 92, Folder 44)
    - Riss Centennial, 1949 (Box 92, Folder 45)
    - S, 1947-1950 (Box 92, Folder 46)
    - Scheftel, Herbert, 1947-1949 (Box 92, Folder 47)
    - Cooper & Powers correspond with Senators and representatives, 1946-1950 (Box 92, Folder 48)
    - Swope, Gerard (Correspondence with Cooper), 1947-1948 (Box 92, Folder 49)
    - Swope, Gerard (Correspondence with Powers), 1949 (Box 92, Folder 50)
    - T, 1949 (Box 92, Folder 51)
    - Turnbull, Phillips R., 1947-1949 (Box 92, Folder 52)
    - U, 1947-1949 (Box 92, Folder 53)
    - V, 1948 (Box 92, Folder 54)
    - The Villager, 1946-1949 (Box 92, Folder 55)
    - Volunteers, 1946-1949 (Box 92, Folder 56)
    - Wagner, Robert F., 1947 (Box 92, Folder 57)
    - Wallender, Arthur W., 1947 (Box 92, Folder 58)
    - Welfare Council of New York City, 1946-1949 (Box 92, Folder 59)
    - Whitmarsh, Francis L., 1948 (Box 92, Folder 60)
    - American Red Cross, 1950-1952 (Box 92, Folder 61)
    - A, general, 1950-1952 (Box 92, Folder 62)
    - Board of Education, 1950-1952 (Box 92, Folder 63)
    - Brooklyn College, 1949-1951 (Box 92, Folder 64)
    - B, general, 1950-1952 (Box 92, Folder 65)
    - Child Care Center, 1950-1952 (Box 92, Folder 66)
    - Civil Defense, 1950-1952 (Box 92, Folder 67)
    - Community Planning Council/ Board, 1951-1952 (Box 92, Folder 68)
    - Condolence letters, undated (Box 92, Folder 69)
    - C, general, 1950-1952 (Box 92, Folder 70)
    - Day Care Council- general, 1950-1952 (Box 92, Folder 71)
    - Day Care Council- minutes, 1950-1952 (Box 92, Folder 72)
    - Department of Health, 1950-1952 (Box 92, Folder 73)
    - Department of Welfare & Day Care Council-minutes of Joint Meetings, 1951-1952 (Box 92, Folder 74)
    - Donations, undated (Box 92, Folder 75)
    - D, general, 1950-1952 (Box 92, Folder 76)
    - F, general, 1950-1952 (Box 92, Folder 77)
    - Gallagher, Irene, 1950-1952 (Box 92, Folder 78)
    - H, general, 1950-1952 (Box 92, Folder 79)
    - Inter-Office Memos, 1950-1952 (Box 92, Folder 80)
    - Mayor Impellitteri; Borough President Isaacs; I, general, 1950-1952 (Box 92, Folder 81)
    - J-K, general, 1950-1952 (Box 92, Folder 82)
    - Local District Planning Board, 1952 (Box 92, Folder 83)
    - L, general, 1950-1952 (Box 92, Folder 84)
    - M, general, 1951-1952 (Box 92, Folder 85)
    - New York University, 1951-1952 (Box 92, Folder 86)
    - N-O, general, 1951-1952 (Box 92, Folder 87)
    - P, general, 1950-1952 (Box 92, Folder 88)
    - Powers, Maxwell- personal, 1949-1952 (Box 92, Folder 89)
    - R, general, 1950- 1952 (Box 92, Folder 90)
    - Simkhovitch, Mary, 1948-1949 (Box 92, Folder 91)
    - S, general, 1950-1952 (Box 92, Folder 92)
    - Thrift Shop, 1950-1952 (Box 92, Folder 93)
    - T-Z, general, 1950-1952 (Box 92, Folder 94)
    - The Villager, 1950-1952 (Box 92, Folder 95)
    - Volunteer Workers, 1950-1952 (Box 92, Folder 96)
    - Washington Square Park Re-development Plan, 1952 (Box 92, Folder 97)
    - Welfare Council of New York City, general, 1950-1952 (Box 92, Folder 98)
    - Welfare Council of New York City, reports, 1950-1951 (Box 92, Folder 99)
    - Board Members- Correspondence, 1953-1954 (Box 92, Folder 100)
  - Subseries 3: Maxwell Powers Files
    - Day Care Council- correspondence, 1953-1954 (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Day Care Council/ Department of Welfare- minutes of Joint Meetings, 1952-1954 (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Day Care Council- Minutes, 1953-1954 (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Powers, Maxwell- personal, 1953-1954 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Board Members- correspondence (A-Z), 1954-1955 (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - B-C, general, 1954-1955 (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - Camp- correspondence, 1954 (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - Camp- correspondence, 1955 (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - Christmas Celebrations, 1948-1955 (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - Condolence letters, 1953-1955 (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - Day Care Council- bulletins, general mailings, ca.1950-1954 (Box 93, Folder 11)
    - Day Care Council- By Laws, member lists, 1953-1955 (Box 93, Folder 12)
    - Day Care Council- statistics, 1954-1955 (Box 93, Folder 13)
    - Day Care Council- correspondence, 1954-1955 (Box 93, Folder 14)
    - Day Care Council- minutes, 1954-1955 (Box 93, Folder 15)
    - Department of Welfare/ Day Care Council- minutes of Joint Meetings, 1954-1955 (Box 93, Folder 16)
    - D-F, general, 1954-1955 (Box 93, Folder 17)
    - Fundraising- monthly reports, 1955 (Box 93, Folder 18)
    - Greenwich Village Fresh Air Fund, 1953-1954 (Box 93, Folder 19)
    - G-J, general, 1954-1955 (Box 93, Folder 20)
    - Inter-office memos, 1954-1955 (Box 93, Folder 21)
    - L-S, general, 1954-1955 (Box 93, Folder 22)
    - New School Committee for PS 41- reports, 1953, undated (Box 93, Folder 23)
    - New School Committee for PS 41- press releases, 1953-1954 (Box 93, Folder 24)
    - New School Committee for PS 41- correspondence, 1952-1955 (Box 93, Folder 25)
    - New York University- correspondence, 1951-1955 (Box 93, Folder 26)
    - New York University- reports, 1947-1955 (Box 93, Folder 27)
    - Powers, Maxwell- personal, 1954-1955 (Box 93, Folder 28)
    - T-Z, general, 1954-1955 (Box 93, Folder 29)
    - Thanksgiving Dinner, 1954 (Box 93, Folder 30)
    - Theatre Department, 1955 (Box 93, Folder 31)
    - Volunteer Workers/ Donors, 1953-1955 (Box 93, Folder 32)
    - Grand Street Boys' Association, 1957-1958 (Box 93, Folder 33)
    - Greater New York Fund, 1957-1958 (Box 93, Folder 34)
    - Greenwich Village Association- correspondence, 1958 (Box 93, Folder 35)
    - Greenwich Village Association- Committee on Narcotics- minutes, 1958 (Box 93, Folder 36)
    - Greenwich Village Association- Committee on Youth, 1957 (Box 93, Folder 37)
    - Greenwich Village Fresh Air Fund, 1957-1958 (Box 93, Folder 38)
    - Group Work- annual reports, 1956-1957 (Box 93, Folder 39)
    - Group Work- staff job descriptions, 1957 (Box 93, Folder 40)
    - Inter-office memos, 1956-1958 (Box 93, Folder 41)
    - Kiwanis Club of Greenwich Village, 1956-1957 (Box 93, Folder 42)
    - New York University/ Greenwich House Workshops, 1955-1958 (Box 93, Folder 43)
    - Powers, Maxwell- personal, 1956-1958 (Box 93, Folder 44)
    - PS 93 Parents' Association- press release/ speech by Powers, 1957 (Box 93, Folder 45)
    - PS 93 Parents' Association- correspondence & statistics, 1956-1957 (Box 93, Folder 46)
    - PS 93 - reports to Commission on Integration of Board of Education, 1956-1957 (Box 93, Folder 47)
    - School of Performing Arts, 1956 (Box 93, Folder 48)
    - Theatre Benefit- Happy Hunting, 1958 (Box 93, Folder 49)
    - Theatre, 1956-1958 (Box 93, Folder 50)
    - Antique Show, 1958-1959 (Box 93, Folder 51)
    - Art Exhibition, 1958-1959 (Box 93, Folder 52)
    - Board Members- correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 93, Folder 53)
    - Christmas Appeal, 1958 (Box 93, Folder 54)
    - Day Care Council- correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 93, Folder 55)
    - Day Care Council- reports/ statistics, 1958 (Box 93, Folder 56)
    - Day Center for Older People, 1957-1958 (Box 93, Folder 57)
    - Donations, 1958-1959 (Box 93, Folder 58)
    - Greater New York Fund, 1958-1959 (Box 93, Folder 59)
    - Greenwich House- correspondence, general, 1958-1959 (Box 93, Folder 60)
    - Greenwich Village Association, 1958-1959 (Box 93, Folder 61)
    - Greenwich Village Fresh Air Fund, 1959 (Box 93, Folder 62)
    - Group Work, 1958-1959 (Box 93, Folder 63)
    - Havens Relief Fund, 1958-1959 (Box 93, Folder 64)
    - Inter-office memos, 1958-1959 (Box 93, Folder 65)
    - Kiwanis Club of Greenwich Village, 1958-1959 (Box 93, Folder 66)
    - New York University, 1958-1959 (Box 93, Folder 67)
    - Powers, Maxwell- personal, 1958-1959 (Box 93, Folder 68)
    - Thanksgiving/ Founders' Day Celebration, 1958 (Box 93, Folder 69)
    - Theatre Benefit- correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 93, Folder 70)
    - Treasurer's Reports, 1958-1959 (Box 93, Folder 71)
    - West Side Association of Community Centers, 1958-1959 (Box 93, Folder 72)
    - Board Members- correspondence, 1962-1964 (Box 93, Folder 73)
    - Child Care Center, 1962-1965 (Box 93, Folder 74)
    - Committee on Housing, 1962 (Box 93, Folder 75)
    - Committee on Village Tensions, 1959-1960 (Box 93, Folder 76)
    - Condolence letters, 1960-1965 (Box 93, Folder 77)
    - Council on Drug Addiction- minutes & correspondence, 1963-1965 (Box 93, Folder 78)
    - Day Care Council- By Laws, 1961, 1964 (Box 93, Folder 79)
    - Day Care Council- correspondence, 1962-1965 (Box 93, Folder 80)
    - Day Care Council- minutes, 1963-1965 (Box 93, Folder 81)
    - Donations, 1960-1965 (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Anti-Poverty Cultural Program- Grant Proposal, 1965-1966 (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - Camp- correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - Camp- reports, 1965 (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - Camp- Trail Blazer Camps- correspondence, 1963-1966 (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - Camp- Trail Blazer Camps- reports on Campers from GH, 1963-1964, 1967 (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - Child Care Center- correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - Christmas Celebration, 1965 (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - Condolence letters, 1965-1966 (Box 94, Folder 9)
    - Day Care Council of New York- financial records, 1965-1966 (Box 94, Folder 10)
    - Day Care Council of New York- general, 1965-1966 (Box 94, Folder 11)
    - Day Care Council of New York- minutes, 1965-1966 (Box 94, Folder 12)
    - Day Care Council of New York- minutes; joint meetings w/ Department of Welfare, 1965-1966 (Box 94, Folder 13)
    - Donations, 1964-1965 (Box 94, Folder 14)
    - Grand Street Boys' Association, 1965-1966 (Box 94, Folder 15)
    - Greater New York Fund, 1958-1965 (Box 94, Folder 16)
    - Greenwich House Counseling Center- studies/ reports, ca.1963-1967 (Box 94, Folder 17)
    - Greenwich House Counseling Center- monthly reports, minutes, 1963-1967 (Box 94, Folder 18)
    - Greenwich House Counseling Center- correspondence, 1963-1967 (Box 94, Folder 19)
    - Greenwich House Counseling Center- financial information; budget, expenses, 1963, undated (Box 94, Folder 20)
    - Greenwich House Counseling Center- miscellaneous, undated (Box 94, Folder 21)
    - Greenwich Village Fresh Air Fund, Inc., 1960-1964 (Box 94, Folder 22)
    - Group Work, 1965-1966 (Box 94, Folder 23)
    - Havens Relief Fund, 1956-1965 (Box 94, Folder 24)
    - Head Start Program, 1965-1966 (Box 94, Folder 25)
    - Kiwanis Club of Greenwich Village, 1965-1966 (Box 94, Folder 26)
    - Local School Board, District 5- correspondence, 1963-1965 (Box 94, Folder 27)
    - Local School Board, District 5- minutes, 1965-1966 (Box 94, Folder 28)
    - Lower West Side Anti-Poverty Program- bulletins, 1965-1966 (Box 94, Folder 29)
    - Lower West Side Anti-Poverty Program- By Laws; criteria for Board of Directors, 1965 (Box 94, Folder 30)
    - Lower West Side Anti-Poverty Program- correspondence, 1964-1966 (Box 94, Folder 31)
    - Lower West Side Anti-Poverty Program- general mailings, 1965-1966 (Box 94, Folder 32)
    - Lower West Side Anti-Poverty Program- minutes; Board, 1966 (Box 94, Folder 33)
    - Lower West Side Anti-Poverty Program- minutes; Planning Committee, 1965 (Box 94, Folder 34)
    - Lower West Side Anti-Poverty Board- press releases; clippings, 1965-1966 (Box 94, Folder 35)
    - Lower West Side Anti-Poverty Program- grant proposal, 1965 (Box 94, Folder 36)